<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview :: Critical Sectors Community, India</title><link>https://cscin.org/docs/index.html</link><description>Critical sector entities and other organisations have no dearth of information and guidance from multiple sources to help them secure their IT systems and networks. Yet, a large number of them continue to suffer downtime and losses due to cyber-attacks. An analysis of successful attacks indicate that most of them succeeded because the entities did not or could not apply the cybersecurity information and guidance effectively.
The documentation in this section attempts to address the gap between knowledge and execution. Many of the insights and perspectives in this section are derived from the practices and processes adopted by organisations having a high level of cybersecurity capability and maturity.</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cscin.org/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://cscin.org/docs/introduction/index.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cscin.org/docs/introduction/index.html</guid><description>The digitalisation initiatives across India have increased significantly, bringing enhanced national productivity, efficiency, growth and quality of service. At the same time, a manifold increase in adverse cyber incidents pose serious danger to the nation’s well-being. Cyber-attacks on critical information infrastructure by organised criminal groups, non-state and state sponsored groups can cause debilitating impact to national security, economy, public health and public safety.
The critical sector entities (CSEs) that own, run, and manage their critical information infrastructure (CII) are solely responsible for the protection of their computer resources (systems, networks, applications, data repositories and identities). The entities are expected and required to use appropriate technology, implement various best practices and build a competent workforce to achieve a high level of cyber resilience.</description></item></channel></rss>