<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home :: Critical Sectors Community, India</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/index.html</link>
    <description>This website has information related to cybersecurity and cyber resilience that is primarily meant for critical sector entities (CSEs) of India. However, the information is usable by entities of other sectors too.&#xA;The Introduction section under Documentation provides a detailed perspective of what this website intends to achieve.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Overview</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/index.html</guid>
      <description>Critical sector entities and other organisations have no dearth of information and guidance from multiple sources to help them secure their IT systems and networks. Yet, a large number of them continue to suffer downtime and losses due to cyber-attacks. An analysis of successful attacks indicate that most of them succeeded because the entities did not or could not apply the cybersecurity information and guidance effectively.&#xA;The documentation in this section attempts to address the gap between knowledge and execution. Many of the insights and perspectives in this section are derived from the practices and processes adopted by organisations having a high level of cybersecurity capability and maturity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/index.html</guid>
      <description>Contact details</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FAQs</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/faqs/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/faqs/index.html</guid>
      <description>FAQs</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/resources/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/resources/index.html</guid>
      <description>Downloadable resources</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>